### Sella Rafaeli, CV: Full-Stack Developer

American Citizen, currently living in Israel (Dec 2017)

sella.rafaeli@gmail.com, https://sellarafaeli.com

#### Skills

I am a very experienced (+15 years) full-stack web developer. I am passionate about producing fast quality work, and enjoy working on complicated, large, mission-critical systems.

I have extensive backend and frontend production experience with Ruby (Rails, Sinatra), Python (Flask, Django), JavaScript ('Vanilla', Vue, React, Angular1, Angular2+, Node), MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Redis, Couchbase, and similar.

Using all of the above I have developed and led development of web products from scratch to massive scale (of traffic, code, and team) for B2C and B2B companies.

#### Education

- **BSc Computer Science**, minor in Psychology, graduated **Magna Cum Laude** (Hebrew University of Jerusalem, Israel)
- Israel's SAT: 786 / 800, top 0.01% in the nation.

# Experience

APRIL 2016 - PRESENT

Full-Stack Web Team Leader, Hysolate (<a href="https://hysolate.com">https://hysolate.com</a>, Cyber-Security product)

- Led web development from day 1.
- Hands-on development and team leadership of enterprise BE web server for cyber-security product (mostly Ruby and MongoDB).
- Hands-on development and team leadership of enterprise FE web app. (mostly Angular2+).

MARCH 2015 - APRIL 2016

CTO, yes.no (Q&A based social network, raised 1M\$. Sold, private)

- Founder, CTO, recruited and managed R&D team of 6, led web development hands-on.
- Expanded architectural overview: http://bit.ly/2CfSL2P

2012 - MARCH 2015

Senior Full-Stack Web Developer, Fiverr (<a href="https://www.fiverr.com">https://www.fiverr.com</a>, Marketplace for services)

- Led development on banking, payment and order flows.
- Led development on Innovation Team.

#### 2009 - 2012

## Hebrew University, BSc Computer Science

- Graduated Magna Cum Laude
- Minor in Psychology

### 2003 - 2008

## Israeli Intelligence Corps, 8200 (classified)

- Intelligence Officer; please ask for references.
- Receiver of multiple IDF awards.

### **Published Works**

- My published articles: <a href="https://sellarafaeli.com/blog/">https://sellarafaeli.com/blog/</a>
- My e-book on Linear Algebra: https://sites.google.com/site/linearit1hujibook/
- My e-book on Algorithms:
  <a href="https://sites.google.com/site/linearit1hujibook/see-also">https://sites.google.com/site/linearit1hujibook/see-also</a>
- My e-book on Git: https://sellarafaeli.wordpress.com/2014/03/23/git-sandbox-book/
- My blog: <a href="https://www.sellarafaeli.com/blog/">https://www.sellarafaeli.com/blog/</a>